Our next exercise examines the use of Bootstrap and
在这个练习里 我们将会学习怎么综合应用 Bootstrap 和 jQuery
JQuery together in particular, using the Bootstrap's JavaScript
特别地 学习同时应用它们来应用 Bootstrap 的 JavaScript 方法
methods in order to control some of the JavaScript components in Bootstrap.
来控制 Bootstrap 中的一些 JavaScript 组件
In this exercise, we're gonna introduce a couple of buttons to control the carousel.
在这个练习里 我们将会引进一系列按钮 来控制我们的轮播
We'll be able to start and
这些按钮将允许我们
stop the slide transitions in the carousel using these buttons.
暂停或继续轮播的滚动
These buttons will be activated using Bootstrap's JS component methods.
这些按钮是通过 Bootstrap 的 JavaScript 组件方法 来激活的
You can see the slide transitions in the index.html page.
在我们 index.html 页面里 我们可以看到 我们的轮播在很漂亮地滚动
Now, you see that we have introduced two buttons at the right corner of
然后在轮播的右下角 你可以看到两个按钮
the carousel, which allow us to control the slide transitions.
这两个按钮就是拿来控制这个轮播的滚动的
We can pause the slide transitions so
我们可以暂停其滚动
that the transitions are completely paused.
从而轮播就会停在当前的页面
We can then resume the slide transitions by clicking on the Resume button there.
接着我们可以继续其滚动
Now these two buttons are gonna be introduced using
这两个按钮都是通过 Bootstrap 的
the Bootstrap's JavaScript paste methods.
基于 JavaScript 的方法来实现的
How do we introduce these controls?
那么具体的实现是怎么样的呢？
We'll go to the index.html page, and
让我们来看看 index.html 的代码
inside the carousel we will introduce the two buttons as a button group.
我们将在轮播这一块代码中通过一个按钮组 来引入两个按钮
Let me add the code, and then we'll come back and review this.
让我来把代码写了 然后你可以研究一下这些代码
You can now see that I have introduced a button group here with the ID
现在 你可以看到我在这里引入了 id="carouselButtons"
"carouselButtons" and this contains two buttons in there.
的一个按钮组 btn-group
There are two buttons, the first one containing
而在这个按钮组里面有两个按钮
the pause glyphicon, inside there.
第一个按钮包含了一个"暂停"的 小 glyphicon 图标
And the second button here, having the play glyphicon inside there.
然后第二个按钮则包含了一个"播放" 的 glyphicon 图标
So these two buttons get added to the carousel.
注意到我是通过在 button 标签中插入 span 标签 来实现的
To position the carousel control buttons correctly,
为了把这个两个控制按钮放在正确的位置
I have added a CSS class here for the carousel buttons.
我针对 carouselButtons 写了一些 CSS 代码
This CSS class gives the right and
在这个 CSS 类里 我把 right 和 bottom 属性
bottom to 0 pixels and the position as absolute.
都设置为了0px 的同时把 position 属性 设置为了绝对定位 absolute
This will move the button group to the bottom right corner of the carousel.
这将会将我们定义的按钮组移到轮播的右下角
Our final modification to the index.html page is to add
我们要做的最后一个改动就是 在这坨代码的最后
the JavaScript code to the end of the page,
加进关键的 JavaScript 代码
just before the end of the body tag.
当然了 加进的代码要在 body 标签的上面
So here, you can see that I have pasted the JavaScript code here with
那么你可以看到我把 JavaScript 代码 粘贴了过来
the $(document).ready(function(){ driving this code here.
注意到 $(document).ready(function(){ 是整段代码的入口
So, inside there, the first thing that I have done
那么在这个入口里面 我做的第一件事
is to set the transition interval to two seconds by specifying for
就是把滚动的间隔设置为了两秒
the mycarousel the interval as 2000.
表现在代码上 就是 interval: 2000
I have also introduced two new functions here, corresponding to the pause and
我同样实现了两个新的函数 这两个函数 分别对应着
the play button that we have just introduced in the carousel.
暂停和继续的行为
For the Pause button, you can see that I am, when the Pause button is clicked,
对于暂停行为 我把它绑定在了 对暂停按钮的点击上
the carousel is going to be paused by calling the .carousel('pause'); method.
具体的实现 就是 .carousel('pause');
Similarly, when the Play button is clicked,
类似的 我们可以定义“继续”行为
the .carousel('cycle'); method is called.
只要写 .carousel('cycle'); 就行了
With these changes, the two control buttons for the carousel are now active.
做完这些后 那两个按钮应该就能用了
So we can now pause the slide transitions,
也就是说我们能通过那两个按钮
as well as resume the slide transitions by clicking the two buttons there.
来暂停轮播的滚动以及继续轮播的滚动了
So again, going back to the web page,
那么回到我们的网页
you can see that I can pause the transitions by clicking the Pause button,
你可以看到我点击这个暂停按钮后
and so the transitions are completely paused at this point.
轮播的滚动停下来了
I can always resume transitions by clicking the Resume
而我想要让它继续滚动时 我总可以通过
button which resumes the transitions of the slides in the carousel.
点击这个继续按钮来做到
This completes this exercise.
以上 我们完成了这次练习
In this exercise we have examined the use of JavaScript-based controls for
在这个练习里 我们学习了如何用 基于 JavaScript 的方法
the Bootstrap Carousel JS component.
来控制 Bootstrap 的 JS 组件轮播 【翻译 - Carefree0910】